RESUME

MANJU DHANWANI

Personal Details:

Birth – 27th May 1978

Address: 3, Devashish Society, Gen. Vaidya Nagar, Nasik-Pune Road, Nasik

Phone – 9371990833 / 0253 – 2598500 E-Mail id – <u>manju_ruchika@rediffmail.com</u>

Education:

B Com. In the year 2000 From BYK College Accounting & Auditing Specialization Computer Application degree course

Professional Summary:

Administration skills, well versed in Accounts reporting, managing office staff performance, scheduling & task delegation, file & records management, proven leadership, organizational & customer relation skills, job title with 16+ years of experience in industry, excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction & doing overall operational improvements, constantly saved cost while increasing profits, eager to contribute to team success through hardwork, clear understanding of task, strong communication skill, motivation to learn, grow & excel in Industry.

Work History:

POWERICA LIMITED, NASIK - MFG. OF DIESEL GENERATING SET

Exp - FROM YEAR 2006 to YEAR 2020

- Handling all the branch activities (Admin, Account, Sales & service)
- Managed CRM database & report generation.
- Making quotations & collecting orders for supply of Gensets.
- Collection of payments from customer & maintaining the record.
- Proper Communication at H.O. & with factories for smooth ordering & dispatching of Genset.
- Handling petty cash expenses & making monthly expense statements.
- Making Web entry in Oracle system, Engineer deputation for commissioning calls & getting the Genset complaints resolved.
- Supported timely & accurate administration task completion.
- Established efficient workflow processes, monitored daily activities of sales & despatches & implemented modification to improve overall effectiveness with staff to develop customer service improvement initiatives.
- Office inventory activities including ordering & stocking.
- Helped employees with day to day work & complex problem by applying motivational analytical strategies.
- Established positive working relationships with colleagues & customer's through regular communication & effective anticipation of needs.

SINDHU SAGAR ACADEMY – (Worked as a Part time teacher)

From the year 2008 to 2016

• Taken the classes from 5th std. to 10th std.

TATA IFOTECH COMPUTER INSTITUTE - (Worked as a counselor)

Exp. – From year 2002 to Year 2004

- To guide students for computer courses.
- Managing time table for faculties , arranging the batches for students & handling students queries.
- Taking the batches for teaching Basic course (MS Word, Powerpoint, Excel, Paint etc.)

MICO BOSCH (Automobile part Manufacturer)

From Year 1998 to 1999

• Worked as a commercial trainee in MVC, PURCHASE & PER dept.